// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Electronic configuration of chromiom (24) is?",
    answer: "[Ar]3d⁵4s¹",
    options: [
      "[Ar]3d⁴4s²",
      "[Ar]3d⁵4s¹",
      "[Ar]3d⁶4s⁰",
      "[Ar]3d⁵4s⁰"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The angular moment of an electronic reducing round the nucleus in k shell given by?",
    answer: "h/2π",
    options: [
      "h/2π",
      "h²/2π",
      "π/2h",
      "h/2π²"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following set of quantum number is not possible for 'P' electron?",
    answer: "n=4,l=1,m=+2 and ms=+1/2",
    options: [
      "n=4,l=1,m=+1 and ms=+1/2",
      "n=4,l=1,m=+0 and ms=+1/2",
      "n=4,l=1,m=+2 and ms=+1/2",
      "=4,l=1,m=-1 and ms=-1/2"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which one of the following molecule has the highest bond?",
    answer: "N2",
    options: [
      "O2",
      "Hcl",
      "N2",
      "H2"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The bond angle in water is?",
    answer: "104°27",
    options: [
      "104°27",
      "90°",
      "107°",
      "120°"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Sugar dissolved in water due to the formation of?",
    answer: "Hydrogen bonding",
    options: [
      "Covalent bond",
      "Ionic bonds",
      "Co-efficient ordinate bonds",
      "Hydrogen bonding"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 7,
    question: "When a saturated solution prepared at a higher temperature is cooled,we get?",
    answer: "Super saturated solution",
    options: [
      "Super cooled mixture",
      "Super saturated solution",
      "An equilibrium mixture",
      "On molar solution"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "An alloy is a homogeneous mixture of?",
    answer: "Two metals",
    options: [
      "Two solids",
      "Two liquids",
      "Two metals",
      "Two non-metals"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Process in which acids[H+] and bases[OH-] react to form salts and water called?",
    answer: "Neutralization",
    options: [
      "Neutralization",
      "H",
      "Hydrogenation",
      "Hydrolysis"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following will make a basic buffer?",
    answer: "100ml of 0.1 MHCL +200ml of 0.1 MNH4OH",
    options: [
      "100ml of 0.1 MHCL +200ml of 0.1 MNH4OH",
      "100ml of 0.1 MHCL +100ml of 0.1 M",
      "100ml of 0.1 Naol +25ml of 0.1 CH3COOH",
      "100ml of 0.1 CH3COOH +100ml of 0.1 M NaOH"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "The no.of electrons involved in redox reaction when a faraday of electricity is passed through an electrolyte in sol is?",
    answer: "6*10²³",
    options: [
      "6*10²³",
      "8*10¹⁹",
      "97100",
      "6*10-²³"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "A sol of silver was electrolyted using it electrodes and a DC current of strength amperes for 965sec the weight of silver (at.wt 108) deposited was?",
    answer: "2.16gm",
    options: [
      "2.16gm",
      "1.08gm",
      "103gm",
      "0.432gm"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 13,
    question: "How many electrons are protect in 1 coloumb?",
    answer: "6.24*10¹⁸",
    options: [
      "6.02*10²¹",
      "6.24*10¹⁸",
      "6.24*10¹⁵",
      "6.02*10¹⁶"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "The charge required to liborate 11.5g of sodium from used chloride is?",
    answer: "0.5F",
    options: [
      "0.5F",
      "1.0F",
      "1.5F",
      "96500 columb"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "The exhausted teolite bed can be regerated by washing with?",
    answer: "Nacl",
    options: [
      "Nacl",
      "dil.NaoH",
      "dil.Hcl",
      "Distilled water"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "A raw water sample has 300ppm calcium ions amd its CaCo3 equilent in ppm is?",
    answer: "625",
    options: [
      "625",
      "750",
      "1500",
      "25"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Voleanisation involves heating of Raw rubber ?",
    answer: "Elementar sulpher",
    options: [
      "Selenium element",
      "Elementar sulpher",
      "A mixture of Se and element Sulphar",
      "A mixture of selenium and sulphur dy-oxide"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "Tinning of iron is an example of?",
    answer: "Cathodic coating",
    options: [
      "Organic coating",
      "Inorganic coating",
      "Anodic coating",
      "Cathodic coating"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "Rusting of iron is catelysed by?",
    answer: "H+",
    options: [
      "Zn²+",
      "OH-",
      "H+",
      "Cl-"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "The medium which reacts with pollutant ?",
    answer: "Sinle",
    options: [
      "Sinle",
      "Speciation",
      "Receptor",
      "Contaminant"
    ]
  },
];